{
    "id": "575b9bebddcb4dd8a171c45dded233cf",
    "title": "Identify the tense form",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a5fecee753924d36bf3deac56b1cb489",
            "title": "Tense Forms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "They had been waiting for the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "past perfect tense active",
                        "past perfect continuous active",
                        "past perfect passive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "India has not won many Olympic gold medals.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "present perfect passive",
                        "present perfect active",
                        "past perfect active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The film was not interesting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "past continuous active",
                        "past continuous passive",
                        "simple past active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy was punished for lying.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "simple past active",
                        "simple past passive",
                        "past perfect active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your order has been shipped.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "present perfect active",
                        "present perfect passive",
                        "simple present active",
                        "simple past active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The house is being built by masons.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "present continuous active",
                        "present continuous passive",
                        "past continuous active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who are you waiting for?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "present continuous tense active",
                        "present continuous tense passive",
                        "simple past active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have been living in this street for well over ten years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "present continuous tense active",
                        "present perfect tense passive",
                        "present perfect continuous tense active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Trains will be running late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "simple future tense active",
                        "simple future tense passive",
                        "future continuous tense active",
                        "future continuous tense passive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news is too good to be true.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "simple present active",
                        "simple present passive",
                        "simple past active"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}